

PENG FEI ZHANG

Front-end Developer

CONTACT

236 988 1101

Richmond, BC CA

EDUCATION

B.A. Psychology

University of British Columbia

2009.09 - 2014.05

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- ReactJS
- SPA
- BEM
- SCSS
- ExpressJS
- Mongoose

ABOUT ME

Hi there, my name is ALVIN, a front-end developer.

I've been teaching myself to code in the past year, with main focus on the front-end. Since I have no prior work experience as a developer, I've prepared a portfolio to showcase my skillset. Click <u>HERE</u> to check it out!

WORK EXPERIENCE

e-Commerce (Amazon FBA)

Self-employed | 2021.05 - 2022.03

- Source products, negotiate terms and prices with suppliers.
- Optimize product listing, advertisement keywords, etc.

OPERATIONS COORDINATOR

Tencent Holdings | 2017.04 - 2021.03

- Assist day to day operations of Tencent Parental Guidance Platform (an app that provides solutions to game addiction).
- Handle administrative duties, project management, etc.
- Work with field experts to produce educational content (topics on addiction, child development, familycommunication, etc).

ACCOUNT REPRESENTATIVE

CIK Telecom | 2014.08 - 2016.11

- Assist customers with account issues: account opening, upgrading, and cancelling etc.
- Refer customer enquiries to technical team members as required.